[
	{
		"id": "1",
		"question": "अ",
		"answer": "a"
	},
	{
		"id": "2",
		"question": "आ",
		"answer": "aa"
	},
	{
		"id": "3",
		"question": "क",
		"answer": "ka"
	},
	{
		"id": "4",
		"question": "च",
		"answer": "cha"
	},
	{
		"id": "5",
		"question": "प",
		"answer": "pa"
	},
	{
		"id": "6",
		"question": "म",
		"answer": "ma"
	},
	{
		"id": "7",
		"question": "य",
		"answer": "ya"
	},
	{
		"id": "8",
		"question": "र",
		"answer": "ra"
	},
	{
		"id": "9",
		"question": "ल",
		"answer": "la"
	},
	{
		"id": "10",
		"question": "त",
		"answer": "ta"
	},
	{
		"id": "11",
		"question": "न",
		"answer": "na"
	},
	{
		"id": "12",
		"question": "व",
		"answer": "va"
	},
	{
		"id": "13",
		"question": "ग",
		"answer": "ga"
	},
	{
		"id": "14",
		"question": "ह",
		"answer": "ha"
	},
	{
		"id": "15",
		"question": "छ",
		"answer": "chha"
	},
	{
		"id": "16",
		"question": "ज",
		"answer": "ja"
	},
	{
		"id": "17",
		"question": "इ",
		"answer": "e"
	},
	{
		"id": "18",
		"question": "द",
		"answer": "da"
	},
	{
		"id": "19",
		"question": "ब",
		"answer": "ba"
	},
	{
		"id": "20",
		"question": "स",
		"answer": "sa"
	},
	{
		"id": "21",
		"question": "ड",
		"answer": "dha"
	},
	{
		"id": "22",
		"question": "ई",
		"answer": "ee"
	},
	{
		"id": "23",
		"question": "घ",
		"answer": "gha"
	},
	{
		"id": "24",
		"question": "श",
		"answer": "sha"
	},
	{
		"id": "25",
		"question": "ट",
		"answer": "ta (soft)"
	},
	{
		"id": "26",
		"question": "ठ",
		"answer": "ta (hard)"
	},
	{
		"id": "27",
		"question": "उ",
		"answer": "u"
	},
	{
		"id": "28",
		"question": "ध",
		"answer": "dha"
	},
	{
		"id": "29",
		"question": "ष",
		"answer": "sha (short)"
	},
	{
		"id": "30",
		"question": "ख",
		"answer": "kha"
	},
	{
		"id": "31",
		"question": "झ",
		"answer": "jha"
	}
]
